Guide to the Bella C. Landauer Collection of Business and Advertising Ephemera 1700-1990 PR 31
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: SCRAPBOOKS
  - WORLD WAR II
    - 1940-1942, BCL vol. 23.5 (Offsite-box SB 202, Folder 1-10)
    - 1942, BCL vol. 23.6 A (Offsite-box SB 203, Folder 1-9)
    - 1942, BCL vol. 23.6 B (Offsite-box SB 204, Folder 1-4)
    - 1942-1943, BCL vol. 23.7 A (pages 1-78) (Offsite-box SB 205, Folder 1-2)
    - 1942-1943, BCL vol. 23.7 B (pages 79-157) (Offsite-box SB 206, Folder 3-4)
    - 1943-1951, BCL vol. 23.8 (Offsite-box SB 207, Folder 1-3)
    - Marshall Plan, etc., BCL vol. 23.9 (Offsite-box SB 208, Folder 1-3)
    - Price Lists from various merchants and wholesalers, 1757-1863 (Offsite-box SB 209)
  - MISCELLANEOUS ALBUMS AND SCRAPBOOKS
    General
    These scrapbooks and collections were compiled by others and acquired by BCL or the N-YHS.
    - Bagg, Edith Adele, album of valentines and cards (gift, 1954) (Offsite-box SB 234, Box SB 210)
    - Behringer, Emily, Frank Leslie's Ladies Journal Cut Paper Patterns book reused as album for scrap, chromos, trade cards, etc. (gift, 1971) (Offsite-box SB 234, Box SB 211)
    - Beer, Alice, mining company stock certificates (Offsite-box SB 212)
    - Bradley, May, album of trade cards, scrap, rewards of merit, and cards (Offsite-box SB 234, Box SB 213)
    - Butler, Robert J., bank notes: vol. 1, leaves 1-128 (Offsite-box SB 214)
    - Butler, Robert J., bank notes: vol. 1, leaves 129-250 (Offsite-box SB 215)
    - Butler, Robert J., bank notes: vol. 2, leaves 1-121 (Offsite-box SB 216)
    - Butler, Robert J., bank notes: vol. 2, leaves 122-249 (Offsite-box SB 217)
    - Butler, Robert J., bank notes: Leather bound volume, unpaged (Offsite-box SB 218)
    - Carney, Hortense, album of greeting cards, trade cards and labels, 1880- (gift, June 24, 1931) (Offsite-box SB 235, Box SB 219)
    - "Centennial Scrap Book" album of scrap, chromos, cards, etc. (gift, Nov. 9, 1953) (Offsite-box SB 235, Box SB 220)
    - [Dann, Helen] album of scrap, greeting cards, and trade cards (Offsite-box SB 235, Box SB 221)
    - Gussow, Kahn & Co./Fashion advertising & graphic design (Offsite-box SB 222)
    - Ingraham, D. Phoenix, scrapbook of invitations, 1899-1902 (Offsite-box SB 223-224)
    - Lefferts, Charles M., album of scrap and theatrical portraits (gift, July 1923) (Offsite-box SB 236, Box SB 225)
    - National Advertising Register (part used as scrapbook) (Offsite-box SB 236, Box SB 226)
    - New York and Providence, RI, trade card album (purchase, Dec. 1971) (Offsite-box SB 227)
    - Strobeck album of Troy, NY, trade cards, scrap, chromos, etc. (gift of Patsy Walters) (Offsite-box SB 228)
    - Van Dyck family scrapbook (Offsite-box SB 237, Box SB 229)
    - Wolfe, Margaret A., scrapbook of invitations. 1880-1881 (Offsite-box SB 236, Box SB 230)
    - Two albums of miscellaneous trade cards and cards (Offsite-box SB 237, Box SB 231)
- Series II: LOOSE EPHEMERA
  Series II: Loose Ephemera is arranaged using the same basic organization system as Series I: Scrapbooks. Most items in this series were once housed inside the scrapbooks, and were removed for preservation or exhibition reasons. Additional material has been added to these files since Landauer's death; it is no longer easy to know what ephemera items originated in Landauer's own collection. Some items have roman numerals written on the verso in pencil - these numbers correspond to Landauer's original scrapbook numbers and are written in her hand. Other material may have one of several stamps that Landauer used to identify her collection.
  Within the general scrapbook-based subject organization, files have been further broken down by type of product, manufacturer, or geographical location where appropriate.
  For ease of access, and to best utilize Landauer's filing system, all loose ephemera (i.e. not pasted in a scrapbook) not found in Series III-VII is housed in Series II. This series is organized into subseries by size. Researchers are advised to consult all three subseries in search of their topics of interest.
  Subseries I: Small Ephemera (usually less than 9 x 12 inches) is housed upright in file boxes.
  Subseries II: Medium Ephemera (between 9 x 12 inches and 14 x 18 inches) is housed flat in boxes. Some material in this subseries was originally pasted into scrapbooks.
  Subseries III: Large Ephemera is housed in flat files. Most of this material had previously been called (by Landauer and N-YHS staff) "posters."
  - Subseries I: SMALL EPHEMERA
    - Advertising (Offsite-box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      includes material from BCL scrapbook 01
      Signs and sign companies
      Trading stamp books
      Miscellaneous
    - Agriculture (Offsite-box 2)
      Includes material from BCL scrapbooks 01 D and E Can and crate labels, 19th and 20th century
      Cheese
      Fruits
      Apples
      Apricots
      Cantaloupes
      Cherries
      Citrus, general
      Crenshaw melons
      Figs
      Grapefruit
      Grapes
      Honeydew melons
    - Agriculture (Offsite-box 3)
      Lemons
      Mangoes
      Melons, general
      Nectarines
      Oranges
      Peaches
      Pears
      Plums
      Pomegranates
      Tangerines
      Produce, general
      Produce, California
    - Agriculture (Offsite-box 4)
      Produce: Florida; New York; New Jersey; Maryland; Texas
      Asparagus
      Celery
      Corn
      Peas
      Peppers
      Sweet potatoes
      Tomatoes
      Vegetables, miscellaneous
      Miscellaneous labels
    - Agriculture (Offsite-box 5)
      Cider presses
      Farm equipment
      Hand tools
      Mills and processing machinery
      Mowers and reapers
      Plows and harrows
      Rakes
      Sowers and drills
      Fertilizers, guano, etc.
      Insecticides, poisons, and traps
      Lawn mowers
      Societies, organizations and publications
    - Animals (Offsite-box 6)
      includes material from BCL scrapbooks 01 A and B
      Cattle
      Dogs
      Feed and food
      Horses
      Medical treatments
      Poultry and birds
      Miscellaneous animals
    - Antiques (Offsite-box 6)
      Numismatics
      Cogan, Edward
      Cook, Henry
      Groux, Daniel
      Guttag Brothers
      Lilliendahl, William A.
      Mint of the United States
      Sage, A.B.
      Woodward, W. Elliot
      Miscellaneous antiques sales, shows and dealers
    - Art (Offsite-box 7)
      includes museums and libraries, with material from BCL scrapbook 01 C-1/2
      Art dealers and galleries
      Art exhibitions: Invitations and tickets; Programs and catalogues
    - Art (Offsite-box 8)
      Artists' materials suppliers
      Brushes, easels and equipment
      Devoe Company
      General supplies
      Paints and colors
      Picture frames (see: FURNITURE, Looking glasses and picture frames)
      Artists' self-promotional materials
      Libraries
      Museums (see also: THEATRICAL ENTERPRISES)
      Sculpture: Public monuments; Rogers groups
    - Beverages (Offsite-box 9)
      including material from BCL scrapbooks 02 A Alcoholic Beverages
      Beer
      Breweries: A-Z, miscellaneous
      Importers and dealers
      Liquors
      Rum
      Scotch/rye/whiskey
      Hermitage Distillery
      Miscellaneous distillers and distributors
      Menus and price lists
      Wine
      Champagne
      Price and drink lists
      Temperance material
    - Beverages (Offsite-box 10)
      Non-alcoholic Beverages
      Chocolate/cocoa: Bensdorp's Royal Dutch Cocoa; Van Houten's Cocoa; Miscellaneous brands
      Cider
      Coffee: miscellaneous brands A-Z; Arbuckle's Ariosa; Chase and Sandborn; Lion Coffee; McLoughlin's
      Coffee Shops and stores
      Juices
      Milk
      Soda: Coca-Cola; Pepsi Cola; miscellaneous brands
      Soda water
      Tea: Great American Tea Company; Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company; Union Pacific Tea Company; miscellaneous stores and importers; invoices and price lists
    - Building (Offsite-box 11)
      including material from BCL scrapbooks 02 B-E
      Architects/builders/carpenters/contractors
      Awnings/shades/shutters (see also: HOUSEHOLD, Shades and blinds)
      Bathing/sanitary fixtures
      Bricks
      Cast iron (see: HARDWARE, Foundries)
      Cement/concrete
      Elevators
      Fences
      Glass/windows
      Lumber/cabinetmakers/woodworkers
      Marble (see also: UNDERTAKERS, Grave markers)
      Masons/plasterers
      Paint Manufacturers
      Paint Merchants
      Painters/decorators/sign painters
    - Building (Offsite-box 12)
      Plumbers
      Roofing/siding
      Stone/plaster/terra cotta
      Wall coatings/Kalsomine/fresco/asbestos, etc.
      Wallpapers/paper hangings
      Manufacturers
      Merchants
    - Business (Offsite-box 13)
      including material from BCL scrapbook 02 and 02-1/2
      Banks and banking
      Buildings and institutions
      Checks
      Financial documents
      Letterhead
      Notes and currency
      Novelty advertising items
      Stock certificates
    - Clothing (Offsite-box 14)
      including material from BCL scrapbooks 03 A-K (see also: DRY GOODS) General merchants
      John Wanamaker
      Canes (see CLOTHING, Umbrellas and Canes)
      Haberdashers
      Hosiery
      Ladies Fashions: Fashion plates; Furs; Gloves; Centemeri & Co.; Harris Brothers
    - Clothing (Offsite-box 15)
      Ladies Fashions: A-Z merchants
      Demorest Emporium of Fashion
      Ehrich & Co.
      Jay-Thorpe Inc.
      Macy's
      O'Neill & Co.
      Skirts
      Undergarments
      Corsets
      Clasps
      Hoops, crinolines, and bustles
      Men's Fashions: Collars (celluloid, paper, and cloth)
    - Clothing (Offsite-box 16)
      Men's Fashion: Merchants
      International
      A-Z retailers
      Baldwin
      Brooks Brothers
      Devlin & Co.
      Harlem & Westchester Clothing Co.
      Hayward & Co.
      Jessup & Co.
      London & Liverpool Clothing Co.
      Paret Co.
      Perego
      Raymond & Co.
      Stadler & Co.
      Vogel Brothers
      Shirts
    - Clothing (Offsite-box 17)
      Military clothiers
      Milliners, hat and cap merchants: A-Z retailers; Genin; O'Neill and Company
      Shoes and boots: Blacking, polish, etc.; A-Z manufacturers; Bixby's; Button's Raven Gloss Dressing; Frank Miller
      Shoe Manufacturers: A-Z miscellaneous; Cable Screw Wire & Standard Fastened; Reynolds Brothers
      Shoe Merchants (see also: DRYGOODS)
    - Clothing (Offsite-box 18)
      Shoe Merchants
      Rubbers and overshoes
      Tailors: A-Z miscellaneous; Nicoll the Tailor
      Umbrellas and Canes
    - Clubs and Societies (Offsite-box 19)
      including material from BCL scrapbook 04
      Animal rights (see also: AGRICULTURE, Societies, organizations)
      Arts and sciences
      Bibliophiles
      Fraternal: Masons; miscellaneous
      Heritage and genealogical
      Historical
      Medical
      Military
      Numismatic
      Patriotic and political
      Professional
      Social
      Sporting and recreation
    - Cotton (Offsite-box 20)
      including material from BCL scrapbook 05
      Auction catalogs
    - Dances and Balls (Offsite-box 20)
      including material from BCL scrapbook 04-1/2
      Dance cards and programs, nineteenth century
      Invitations and tickets
      Fire company balls
      Military balls
      Eighteenth and nineteenth centuries, miscellaneous dances and balls
      Twentieth century dances and balls
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 21)
      National A-Z
      Colorado
      Connecticut: A-Z towns; New Haven; Waterbury-R.S. Woodruff
      Illinois: A-Z towns; Chicago-A-Z druggists-Bucklen & Co., Humiston, Keeling & Co., Pioneer Drug Store
      Indiana: A-Z towns; Elkhart; Dr. Miles' Medical Company
      Iowa: Des Moines; Chamberlain Medicine Company
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 22)
      Kansas
      Maine
      Maryland
      Massachusetts: A-Z towns; Boston-A-Z druggists, F.M. Keeler & Co., Fox, Fultz & Co., Seth W. Fowle & Co., Howe & French, Wm. C. Stimpson, Weeks & Potter, Mrs. Winslow's, C.H.& F. Day; Lowell-Ayer & Co., C.I. Hood & Co.; Stoneham-C.O. Currier
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 23)
      Michigan
      Minnesota
      Missouri
      New Hampshire: A-Z towns; Concord
      New Jersey: A-Z towns, Atlantic City, Jersey City, Newark, New Brunswick-Johnson & Johnson, Rahway, Merck & Co., Woodbury, G.G. Green
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 24)
      New York City: A-Q druggists
      Brandreth Caswell, Massey Co. Hegeman & Co. Humphrey's
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 25)
      New York City: R-Z druggists
      Schiffeling & Co. Squibb & Son Van Duzer & Co. Wrecker Pharmacy
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 26)
      New York State:
      A-Z towns
      Albany
      Buffalo: A-Z druggists; World's Dispensary Medical Association
      Cape Vincent
      Granville: Baldwin & Co.
      Hudson
      Kinderhook: Frank Ball
      Lockport
      Middletown
      Rochester
      Saratoga Springs
      Tarrytown: Sackett & Co.
      Troy
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 27)
      Ohio
      Pennsylvania: A-Z towns; Philadelphia- A-Z druggists, B. Harper Diehl, Dr. D. Jayne & Son, Schenk's; Warren- Hazeltine
      Rhode Island
      South Carolina
      Tennessee
      Texas
      Vermont: A-Z towns; Bellow's Falls-A-Z druggists, Geo. F. Woods
    - Druggists (Offsite-box 28)
      Vermont continued: A-Z druggists; Henry, Johnson & Lord; Peck & Spear; Humphrey's; Fredrick & Francis Fenn & Co.; John F. Henry & Co.; M.K. Paine
      Virginia
      Washington, D.C.
      Wisconsin
    - Chemists and Chemicals (Offsite-box 29)
      includes material from BCL scrapbooks 4A-4F
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 29)
      BCL scrapbooks 4A-4F dismantled into these boxes
      Blood Purifiers:
      A-Z brands
      Burdock Blood Bitters
      Dr. Green's Blood Bitters
      Dr. Morse's Syrup of Yellow Dock Root
      Paine's Celery Compound Tonic
      Parker's Ginger Tonic
      Peruvian Syrup
      Robinson's Sura-Cura
      Sarsaparilla- Ayer's, Brown's
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 30)
      Sasparilla- C.I. Hood, Scovill's, Miscellaneous
      Tarrant's Seltzer Aperient
      Tonics and Bitters
      Vegetine
      Dr. Walker's California Vinegar Bitters
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 31)
      Children's Remedies:
      Mrs. Winslow's Soothing Syrup
      Digestives:
      Dr. Arnold's Balsam
      Ayer's Cathartic Pills
      Angostura Bitters
      Brown's Iron Bitters
      Hostetter's Stomach Bitters
      Plantation Bitters
      Sulphur Bitters
      Tippecanoe Bitters
      Willard's Golden Seal Bitters
      Miscellaneous bitters
      Caroid and bile salts
      Castor oil
      Castoria
      Figs and fig syrups
      Gastrine
      Dr. Henri Guillard's Persuaders
      Intestinal (misc. Cholera and Dysentery)
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 32)
      Digestive:
      Laxatives
      Liver and kidney:
      Buchu preparations
      Carter's Little Liver Pills
      Craig Kidney Cure
      Doan's Kidney Pills
      Dr. Grosvenor's Liver Aid
      Hood's Vegetable Pills
      Hunt's Remedy
      Dr. Jayne's Sanative Pills
      Dr. Kilmer & Co.
      Dr. McLane's Liver Pills
      Mandrake pills
      Schenck's Mandrake Pills
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 33)
      Warner's Safe Cure
      Murray Charcoal Tablets
      Pepsin
      Pills, miscellaneous
      Powders and Salts, miscellaneous
      Salts, miscellaneous
      Schenck's Seaweed Tonic
      Seidlitz powders
      Seven Bark s Spring waters
      Tonics, miscellaneous
      Exercise (see: SPORTS, Gymnasiums)
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 34)
      External remedies:
      Baths and bath salts
      Eye treatments
      Foot care
      Corn treatments
      Liniments, ointments and salves:
      Dalley's Magical Pain Extractor
      Ma-le-na
      Medicated soaps
      Merchant's Gargling Oil
      Minard's Liniment
      Renne's Magic Oil
      St. Jacob's Oil
      Sapanule
      Miscellaneous salves
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 35)
      Petroleum products:
      Petrolina
      Vaseline
      Piles and hemorrhoids
      Plasters:
      Allcock's (see also: DRUGGISTS, New York City, Brandreth)
      Benson's Capcine
      Carter's
      Court plasters
      Johnson & Johnson
      Mitchell's
      Paine's Green Mountain
      Pond's Extract
      Miscellaneous plasters
      Skin aids
      Witch hazel
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 36)
      Female Remedies:
      Burdock's Blood Bitters
      Carter's Iron Pills
      Dr. Marchisi's Uterine Catholicon
      Hormone treatments
      Lydia E. Pinkham's Vegetable Compound
      Wines and cordials
      Fever and Ague Treatments:
      Ayer's Ague Cure
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 37)
      Indian Remedies:
      Dr. Morse's Indian Root Pills
      Kickapoo Indians
      Wright's Indian Vegetable Pills
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 38)
      Medicinal Foods:
      Beef extracts
      Best Tonic
      Eskay's Food
      Ginger
      Grains
      Horlick's Malted Milk
      Imperial Granum
      Lactated foods, miscellaneous
      Malt Bitters
      Malt extracts
      Mellin's Food
      Mineral spring waters
      Murdock Liquid Food
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 39)
      Nestle's Milk Food
      Quaker Bitters
      Ridge's Food
      Root beers
      Wells Richardson Lactated Food
      Wheat Bitters
      Wines and spirits
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 40)
      Nervous Disorders:
      Carter's Little Nerve Pills
      Dr. Green's Nervura
      Horsford's Acid Phosphate
      Nichols' Bark & Iron
      Pleis
      Cocoa remedies
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 41)
      General Pain Remedies:
      Antikamina Tablets
      Bayer
      Bromo-Seltzer
      Pain-ine
      Perry Davis' Vegetable Pain Cure
      Dr. Radcliffe's Seven Seals or Golden Wonder
      Headache Remedies:
      Crosby's Five Minute Cure
      Dr. Metter's Headache Pills
      Miscellaneous pills and powders
      Opiates
      Toothache Remedies
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 42)
      Panaceas:
      Electric oils
      Dr. Thomas' Electric Oil
      Electricity:
      Batteries
      Belts
      Elixirs:
      Gargling oils
      Globe Pills
      Hamlin's Wizard Oil
      Health chairs
      Herbal remedies
      Compound Oxygen
      Quassia cups
      Shaker remedies
      Wampole's Preparation
      Wells' Health Renewer
      Physical Culture (see: SPORTS, Gymnasiums)
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 43)
      Respiratory Remedies:
      Allergy Cures:
      Excelsior Asthma Remedy
      Schiffman's German Asthma Cure
      Balsams:
      A. David Ashley's Honey Balsam
      Dr. Carter's Balsam
      Mrs. Dinsmore's
      Dr. Hall's Balsam
      Hartshorn's Cough Balsam
      Porter's Cough Balsam
      Wistar's Balsam of Wild Cherry
      Cattarh Cures:
      Norwegian Balm
      Piso's Cure
      Cod Liver Oil
      Scott's Emulsion
      Wilbur's Cod Liver Oil
      Cold Pills
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 44)
      Cordials: Fairbanks Rock Cordials
      Cough Drops: Hill's Casara Quinine; James' Cough Pills; Lutted's Cough Drops; Miscellaneous
      Inhalants: Mentholatum; Vicks; Miscellaneous
      Lozenges
      Syrups: A.C.D. Cough Syrup; Acker's English Remedy; Dr. Seth Arnold's Cough Killer; Ayers' Cherry Pectoral; Boschee's German Syrup; Grobecker's; Higgins T & C Compound; Dr. Jayne's
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 45)
      Respiratory Cures
      Syrups: Joy to the World; Dr. King's New Discoveries; Miller's Compound Syrup; Papillon Cough Cure; Red Star Cure; Rye & Rock; Schenck's Medicines; Shiloh's Consumption Cure; Tar-Liquorice; Miscellaneous
      Troches: Brown's Bronchial Troches; Miscellaneous
      Miscellaneous respiratory cures
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 46)
      Sanatariums
      Sexual disorders and diseases
      Specific aids:
      Crutches
      Disinfectants
      First aid
      Habits cured
      Invalid's aids
      Opiate prescription forms
      Prosthetics
      Surgical instruments
      Syringes and thermometers
      Trusses and supports
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 47)
      Vermifuges: Comstock's Dead Shot Pellets; Dr. Jayne's Tonic; Miscellaneous
      Vitamins: Pamphlets; Squibb; Unicap; Upjohn; Miscellaneous
    - Drugs and Medicines (Offsite-box 48)
      Related material:
      Books and circulars
      Institutions
      Medicine labels
      Physicians
      Poison
      Preventative medicine
      Products for physicians
      Promoting healthful practices
      Vaccinations
    - Dry Goods/Department Stores (Offsite-box 49)
      Braid, ribbon, and other trimmings
      Buttons
      Dry Goods Merchants, International: Jevons & Mellor
      Dry Goods Merchants, National: A-Z companies; Gilchrist; Landauer
      Dry Goods Merchants, New York City: A-Z companies; B. Altman & Co.; Bergdorf-Goodman; Bloomingdales; Denning's; Hannigan & Bouillon
    - Dry Goods/Department Stores (Offsite-box 50)
      Dry Goods Merchants, New York City: John E. Kaughran & Co.; LeBoutillier Brothers; Lord & Taylor; Macy's; O'Neill and Company; E. Ridley & Son; Stern Brothers; A.T. Stewart & Co.
      Dry Goods Merchants, New York State: Frear's Troy Cash Bazaar; Miscellaneous companies
      Needles, pins, hooks, etc.
      Patterns: Clothing, Needlework
      Silk manufacturers and merchants
      Textile labels (from bales, bolts, and sheets)
    - Dry Goods/Department Stores (Offsite-box 51)
      Thread Manufacturers:
      Barbour Brothers
      Belding Brothers
      Brook's
      Chadwick and Brother
      Clark's (Mile-End Spool Cotton, O.N.T. Spool Cotton, Jumbo series, "National Flower Series," Paper doll series, Storybooks)
      Coats Mills
      Corticelli
      Cutter and Company
      Kerr and Company
      Merrick Thread Company
      Willimantic Linen Company
      Miscellaneous manufacturers
      Woolen goods (see: WOOL)
      Yarn
    - Electricity (Offsite-box 52)
      Electric supply and lighting
      Recording devices
      Telegraph (Morse, Western Union,Miscellaneous companies)
      Telephone Companies (American Telephone & Telegraph, New York Telephone, Miscellaneous)
      Telephone Equipment
      Miscellaneous Electricity
    - Food (Offsite-box 53)
      (includes material from BCL scrapbooks 06 A-I)
      Bakers and baking
      Baking powder
      Bread
      Candy and confectioners (see also: Chocolate)
      Cereals
      Chewing gum
      Chocolate and cocoa (Baker & Co., Maillard, Runkel Brothers, Miscellaneous brands)
      Coconut
      Cornstarch
      Crackers
    - Food (Offsite-box 54)
      Dairy products:
      Ice cream
      Milk, condensed
      Extracts and flavorings
      Fish
      Flour (Hecker's, Pillsbury's, Miscellaneous)
      Fruit and produce
    - Food (Offsite-box 55)
      Grocers, retail (New York City, Miscellaneous)
      Grocers, wholesale (Austin, Nichols Co., Thurber & Co., Miscellaneous)
      Infant and baby foods (see: DRUGS AND MEDICINES, Medicinal foods)
      Jellies
      Lard
      Meat:
      Armour & Co.
      Beef
      Butchers and meat markets
      Canned meat (Libby, McNeill & Libby, Wilson Packing Co., Miscellaneous)
    - Food (Offsite-box 56)
      Meat Extracts (see: DRUGS AND MEDICINES)
      Mincemeat
      Pork products
      Oats
      Oils
      Oysters
      Pickles and preserves
      Poultry
      Salt
      Soda and saleratus
      Soup
      Spices and condiments
      Sugar
      Vinegar
      Yeast
    - Furniture (Offsite-box 57)
      includes material from BCL scrapbooks 06 K-L
      Auctions and dispersals
      Chairmakers
      Dealers and merchants (Cowperthwait & Company, Jordan and Moriarty, Miscellaneous)